What are you working on today?
Today, I'm going to be on a show called Blarney, a Tochigi brand.
I'm going to be a regular on the show.
I'll do my best to report on the show.
I'll do my best!
Style, you know the word.
It's a style, you know.
I'm not that good at it.
I want you all to see the charm of Tochigi.
I'll do my best!
Hello everyone!
I'm Kyohara Saito from Ikolab.
I'm 19 years old and from Tochigi Prefecture.
I'm going to introduce the charms of Tochigi.
I also want to share the charms of Tochigi with you all.
I hope to share the charms of Tochigi
I hope I can share the charms of Tochigi with you.
I will do my best!
I'm still a little nervous.
I feel nervous when I'm alone.
I feel that I am always helped by the members.
I feel it deeply.
Good morning!
I took this picture from the catalogue of the actual story Bi 150 раз, jugs Art Flores
First, феййсst, this time, let's make it.
And then she goes around Does he want to see it again.
She gave up, but in the end Sh ventilation
Jang!
He doesn't want to eat it
I'm going to eat it
Only recommended things
I'm not a beginner
Yes, I am
Yes, you are.
Log's coffee is very easy to drink.
Yes, it is.
Cafe au lait is a staple.
What can I say?
I don't know if you can tell how good it tastes.
The expression on your face.
I don't know.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Delicious.
That's normal.
It's good. It's good.
I'll go there next time.
It's important to keep your eyes open
Introduction of
I almost went through the pennels of this mark
There is a store where you can stand up for a ride
It's a very nice ride.
I'm very interested in all of them, but
but my vocabulary is still too limited.
I'm so frustrated that I can't communicate
I should be able to tell you more!
It's a wonderful pastry!
Thank you very much!
Butter Cousin
Strawberry flavor
Well, at first...
I've been curious about it for a long time.
Strawberry flavor
I'd like to try it.
Yes.
Yum.
Delicious!
What?
There's a lot of butter in it, and it goes really well with the strawberries.
It's really delicious, so delicious I don't remember what I said...
I wonder if it's from winter... I have a song that keeps my emotions to myself, so I'm not sure if the taste is right...
I'm wondering if I can get the taste right now, but there's something I really want to have.
If you've never had it, I want you to try it.
I'd like you to try it this time.
I went to Tochigi to visit the wall and ate a lot of Tochigi's delicious food.
It was a really happy time!
It's good, isn't it?
No, no, no, it's fine!
Boo-hoo!
Hey!
Thank you very much for your time at the school.
It was a lot of fun to record, and I feel the same way. It's difficult to communicate with you.
I feel again how difficult it is to communicate with everyone, but I'm so happy when I do.
This was my second time to play a major role.
But I think I did a little better than last time.
I will continue to do my best to make the grass bridge work on my own.
I'll continue to do my best so that I can make grass bridges by myself.
I'd be very happy if you could see my growth. And I'd be happy if you could drink a lot of milk in Tochigi.
I'd be happy if you could see it.
What is it?
I want to be one of the site characters, and I'd like to be one of you.
I'd like to be one of you and I'd like you to become one of us. I'd like you to spread the charm of our region throughout the country.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy, thank you very much.
I'm so happy because it's always been my dream to spread the charm of the local area to all of our fans nationwide.
I'm so glad to hear that.
I'm so happy because I've been given this opportunity to be an ambassador for the future.
I'll do my best to spread the charm of the future to as many people as possible.
I'll do my best to make it another attraction for many people now that I'm an ambassador for the future.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I'm from udk.
Four divorced.
Thank you very much.
Lino from ani.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yes, it was.
I would like to dedicate the joy of being a Tochigi Future Ambassador.
I'm the future ambassador of Tochigi of my dreams!
I will tell the charm of Tochigi
And let many people know about it!
Oh...
Are you okay? This is really difficult.
Yes, I'm here at the Tochigi Prefectural Government today.
Today is the inauguration ceremony for this year's Future Ambassadors. I'm going to be inaugurated once again.
I've been so enthusiastic today that I thought I'd come in mature clothes or something,
I thought I was going to wear something mature, but it's so flashy inside that I might as well wear a coat. It's so flashy inside that it might even be good to wear a coat. Look at this. Look at this flashy one-piece.
There is a character named Miyari-chan from Utsunomiya, and I love her,
Sakura? Satsuki? She wears it on her head and it looks like this. She wears something like this on her head,
So I thought this was the one, and I wore it today, but it is more flashy than I thought it would be. I wondered if everyone would wear such a flashy pin in a suit.
I'm not sure if I can handle it.
I hope I can express my enthusiasm in my own way. I will do my best.
I look forward to working with you.
Congratulations!
We will now hold the commissioning ceremony for Ambassador Hirai Tochigi.
Letter of commission, Mr. Chihara Saito.
I hereby commission you as Ambassador Hirai of Tochigi.
April 17, 2024, June 1, 2024,
Volume 3, Number 10!
You're like a little girl, Neary.
Yes, you are proud and weak, aren't you?
That's true, isn't it?
I'm a pretty young fan or something.
A wide range of issues.
I'd like to study my Tarot a lot and spread the word more.
I hope I can study Tarot more and more and spread the word.
I'm sure you will have the experience of playing a role in the show in the future.
Yes, I've never worked alone before, so I'm still nervous about the show.
I'm having a lot of fun trotting out the role, and I hope to do my best while improving my reporting skills to convey the charm of the role.
Please love Tochigi a lot!
I hope you are all right. It was like a dream and it was over in a second.
I wanted to ask you some questions, but I was too nervous.
I was so happy to have this precious time with you.
I was so happy to be able to realize once again that I am a future ambassador of Tochigi.
I'm so happy to have become a future ambassador.
I will never forget this initial feeling, and I will always do my best.
I will do my very best.